W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Agencies, Boards, and Commissions, 1912-1980, undated; 1
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Resolutions, 1976-1978, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Statements, 1973-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Tennessee-Tombigbee Waterway Project, Memorandum, 1978 December (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Underground Injection Control Program, Draft of Regulations, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), Correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), Brief and Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Export-Import Bank, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Farm Credit Administration, Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Farm Credit Administration (FCA), Circulars, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Farm Credit Administration (FCA), Correspondence, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Farm Credit Administration (FCA), Correspondence, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Farm Credit Administration (FCA), Correspondence and Legislative Act, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), Correspondence, 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), Correspondence, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1970-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), District Airports, Correspondence, Layouts, and Surveys, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (FAA), Eula Heath, Correspondence, Aviation User Charges, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Federal Commission on Paperwork, Clipping and Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Citizenbander (CB) Regulations, Correspondence and Petitions, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Clippings and Press Releases, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Clippings and Press Releases, 1971-1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Community Antenna Television Service, Clippings and Correspondence (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Community Antenna Television Service, Clippings and Correspondence (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Dockets, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Clippings, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Resolutions, 1956-1962 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Dockets, 1963-1967 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Resolutions, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Petitions, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Dockets, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Emergency Broadcast System, Plan, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Reports and Statements, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), Waco, Television, Clippings and Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Federal Council for Science and Technology, Report, “Federal Water Resources Research Program for Fiscal Year 1969”, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (FDIC), Correspondence, 1960-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Campaign Guides, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Federal and State Election Laws (1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Federal and State Election Laws (2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Federal Election Campaign Act of 1974, Correspondence and Report, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), “Federal Register”, Advisory Opinion Requests, 1975 June-December (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), “Federal Register”, Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Legislative History of Campaign Act of 1974, Bill and “Congressional Record”, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Legislative History of Campaign Act of 1974, Reports (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Notices, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Revision of Federal Election Campaign Act Amendments, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Sample Forms, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Summary of Advisory Opinion Requests, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Texas Election Laws, Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Federal Election Commission (FEC), Upholstery Bill, Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence and Statements, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Correspondence and Clippings, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Pamphlets, circa 1970’s (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Reports, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Federal Energy Administration (FEA), Senate Resolution, 1973 December (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board (FHLBB), Correspondence, 1964-1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Federal Land Bank (FLB), Correspondence, 1951-1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Federal Maritime Commission (FMC), Correspondence, Chairman John Harllee, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Federal National Mortgage Association (FNMA), Correspondence, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Federal Power Commission (FPC), Brazos River, Notices and Resolutions, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Federal Power Commission (FPC), Correspondence and Reports, 1955-1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Federal Power Commission (FPC), Correspondence and Resolutions, 1974-1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Federal Power Commission (FPC), Report, “Typical Electric Bills Cities of 50,000 Population and More”, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Federal Railroad Administration (FRA), Correspondence, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Federal Reserve Bank, Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Federal Reserve Board, Credit Terms on Automobiles, Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Federal Reserve Board, Press Releases and Regulations, 1975-1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Federal Reserve System, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Federal Security Agency (FSA), Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Clippings and Press Releases, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Correspondence, 1952-1963 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), “Federal Register”, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Funeral Industry Practices, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Reports and Statements, 1957-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Federal Works Agency (FWA), Correspondence, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) of the United Nations, Correspondence and Literary Productions, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO) of the United Nations, Proceedings, 1957 November (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, Correspondence, Legal Decisions, and Press Releases, 1955-1958 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, Correspondence and Legal Decisions, 1962-1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, Semi-annual Report, 1956 December (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Operations Administration (FOA), Correspondence, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Army Nonappropriate Fund Insurance and Retirement Plan, Investigation, 1967-1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Comptroller General, Reports, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Newsletters, “Monthly List of GAO Reports”, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Reports, General, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Report, “Budgetary and Fiscal Information Needs of the Congress”, 1972 February (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), Reports, “General Accounting Office Publications”, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Announcements, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Clippings and Press Releases, 1957-1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Consumer Product Information, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Consumer Product Information, Correspondence, Pamphlets, and Press Releases, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Consumer Product Information, Correspondence and Pamphlets, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Consumer Product Information, Indexes and Press Releases, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Federal Surplus Property Program, Correspondence and Legislative Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Local Casework, Clippings and Press Releases, 1972-1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Local Casework, Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Local Casework, Printed Materials and Resolutions, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Nuchols Air Conditioning Company, Incorporated, Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Printed Materials, 1949-1952 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Printed Materials and Pamphlets, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Printed Materials, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Stock Catalogs, 1937-1939 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), Waco Social Security Office, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Correspondence, 1955-1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Correspondence and Forms, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Government Depository Libraries, Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), Report to Congress, Comptroller General, 1977 November 25 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Housing Agencies, Copperas Cove, Housing Shortage, Correspondence and Forms, 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence and Printed Materials, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence and Photographs, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence and Press Releases, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Housing Agencies, Correspondence, 1966-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Housing Agencies, Killeen, Housing, Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Housing Agencies, Press Releases, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Housing Agencies, “Reader’s Digest”, “The Mounting Scandal of Urban Renewal”, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Housing Agencies, U.S. Housing Act of 1937 as Amended, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency (HHFA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency (HHFA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency (HHFA), Urban Renewal Manual, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Indian Claims Commission, Correspondence, 1954-1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Inter-American Development Bank (IDB), Correspondence, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Interagency Task Force for Indochina Refugees, State Department, Contacts, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - International Trade Commission, Annual Report, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - International Trade Commission, Briefs, Clippings, and Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - International Trade Commission, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - International Trade Commission, Potters Industry Incorporated, Correspondence and Reports, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - International Trade Commission, Unalloyed Unwrought Zinc, Press Releases, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Clippings and Press Releases, 1967-1974, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1954-1964 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Correspondence, Press Releases, and Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Dockets, 1951-1953 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Dockets and Orders, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Dockets and Notices, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Dockets and Notices, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Dockets and Orders, 1973-1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Petitions and Resolutions, 1970, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Reports, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Resolutions, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Southern Pacific Company, Correspondence and Dockets, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), Statement, 1972 March (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Library of Congress, American Bicentennial, Printed Materials, 1974-1978 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, 94th Congress Legislative Status Checklist, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, American Bicentennial, “Time”, 1976 July (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, “Bibliography on the State of Texas”, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, Correspondence and Guidelines, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, Major Issues System, Briefs, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, Major Issues System, Briefs, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, Multilithed Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Library of Congress, Congressional Research Service, Telephone Directory, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Library of Congress, “Congressional Research Service Bulletin”, 1978 February-March (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Library of Congress, “Congressional Research Service Review”, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Library of Congress, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Library of Congress, Directories, 1959-1962 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Library of Congress, Frank Oltorf, Correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Library of Congress, Legislative Reference Service, “Digest of Public General Bills and Resolutions”, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Library of Congress, Legislative Reference Service, Reports, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Library of Congress, Major Issues System, Pamphlets and Updates, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Library of Congress, Monthly Calendar of Events, 1978 February-August (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Library of Congress, New Services Available, Updates, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Library of Congress, Pamphlet, “Services to Congress”, 1978 April (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Library of Congress, Poetry and Literature, Programs, 1978 February-May (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Library of Congress, Printed Materials, 1959-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Library of Congress, Tax Seminar Series, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Library of Congress, U.S. House and Senate Committees and Subcommittees, Lists, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Mutual Security Agency, Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - National Advisory Council on Extension and Continuing Education, Correspondence, 1975 August (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Correspondence, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Educational Briefs and Fact Sheets, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Langley Research Center Working Paper #490, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), “National Geographic”, Periodicals, 1966 October-November (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Photographic Materials, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), Rodd Field Enterprise, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), “Selling to NASA”, Booklet, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Archives, Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - National Archives, Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - National Archives, Correspondence, 1971-1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Association of Broadcasters (NAB), Booklet, “Political Broadcast Catechism”, 1976 March-May (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - National Commission on Marihuana and Drug Abuse, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - National Council on the Aging (NCOA), Report, “Campaign 1974: Toward a Responsive Social Policy for the Elderly” (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - National Credit Union Administration (NCUA), Correspondence, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)